clickedindia.net 2017-04-23

# Privacy Policy - ClickedINDIA

At ClickedINDIA, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit ClickedINDIA, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

We collect information from you when you register on our site, post a product, post a tradeleads, subscribe to our newsletter, subscribe for trade alert, respond to a survey or fill out a form. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, mobile number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### Use Of information 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * Your Business Listing  
(Any user can see your business infomation, products, buy offers, sell offers etc,. on our Website)
  * To process transactions
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
  * To send periodic emails, newsletters, trade alerts  
(The email address you provide for processing, will only be used to send you information and updates, trade alerts and newsletters.)

#### How do we protect your information? 

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you post a product, post tradeleads, inquiries , or access your personal information. 

Remember to sign out of your account and close your browser window when you have finished your work.

while we try to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk.

#### Public Access to Information

The information you provide like profile infomation, contact infomation, business infomation, products, tradeleads and other infomation will be made available to all users of our website. 

#### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site. 

#### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features.

We also use third party advertisements on ClickedINDIA to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. 

#### DoubleClick DART Cookie

.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on ClickedINDIA.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to ClickedINDIA and other sites on the Internet.   
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html 

This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

In addition, for the avoidance of doubt, ClickedINDIA does not guarantee the Program will be operable at all times or during any down time   

  1. caused by outages to any public Internet backbones, networks or servers, 
  2. caused by any failures of Your equipment, systems or local access services, 
  3. for previously scheduled maintenance or 
  4. relating to events beyond ClickedINDIA's (or its wholly owned subsidiaries') control such as strikes, riots, insurrection, fires, floods, explosions, war, governmental action, labor conditions, earthquakes, natural disasters, or interruptions in Internet services to an area where ClickedINDIA (or its wholly owned subsidiaries) or Your servers are located or co-located. 

#### Changes to Privacy Policy

if we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page

#### Contacting us

if there are any questions regarding this privacy and policy you can contact us using given infomation.

info@clickedindia.com  
support@clickedindia.com
